(Howard:)And you love the sound
of your own voice.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, well, of course I do.
(Sheldon:)Listen to it.
(Sheldon:)It's like an earful
of melted caramel.
(Leonard:)Look, most importantly,
(Leonard:)this will let you move on
and study dark matter.
(Sheldon:)It is true that many of
my heroes have taken students
under their wings:
(Sheldon:)Feynman, Einstein, Professor X.
(Sheldon:)Humorously,
(Sheldon:)in the case of Professor X,
(Sheldon:)some of his students
actually had wings.
(Sheldon:)That's rich.
(Sheldon:)I'll use that one
to lighten the mood
(Sheldon:)after my entire class
fails the midterm.
(Amy:)Measuring starfish
serotonin levels in response
(Amy:)to one point two molar
stimulation of pleasure cells.
(Amy:)You like that, don't you?
(Amy:)That's right, say my name.
(Skype ringtone playing)